<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NotScattergories</string>

    <string name="play_btn_str">Play Now!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game">GameActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="cat_placeholder"> Things that are really fun</string>

    <string name="rulesTitle">How to play NotScattegories</string>
    <string name="gotIt">Got it!</string>
    <string name="rules" translatable="false"> \n \nOne player starts the timer. In the time allotted, each player must attempt to think of and write down a word or term that fits each of the categories and starts with the displayed letter. Any number of words in the answer is allowed, as long as the first word starts with the correct letter.  \n \nFor example, with a category of \"vegetable\" and a letter of \"C\", words such as \"cauliflower\", \"carrot\" and \"collard greens\" are acceptable, but \"broccoli\" is not (wrong initial letter), nor is \"citrus\" (wrong category).  \n \nAlliteration is encouraged; Ronald Reagan is worth 2 points, and Hubert Horatio Humphrey is worth 3. \n \nWriting a bad answer is still better than no answer though because there is always the possibility that the group playing will accept the answer.  \n \nFor example, \"citrus\" is \"vegetable\" in the sense referring to the entire plant kingdom, i.e. neither \"animal\" nor \"mineral\". \n \nAll players stop writing when the timer is finished. Following the list, each player, in turn, reads their answer for each category. Players score zero points for an answer that duplicates another answer in that round, and one point for an answer no other player has given. You cannot have more than one answer on a line for each number. Acceptable answers that are proper nouns using alliteration score one point for each word using the letter.  \n \nIf for some reason a player thinks someone\'s answer does not fit the category (for instance, \"knuckle\" for the category \"types of sandwich\") a player may challenge that answer. When challenged, all players vote on the validity of that answer. If the vote is a tie, the vote of the player who is being challenged is thrown out. \n \nIn the case of proper nouns, all parts of the answer will be counted as adequate provided one begins with the letter in play. For example, in the case of U.S. Presidents using the letter \"S\", an acceptable answer would be Harry S. Truman, as his middle name is the letter \"S.\" Martin Sheen, however, was never a U.S. President, and therefore is not a valid answer, rewarding zero points. Note: This rule does not apply to book titles, such as \"The Count of Monte Cristo.\" \n \nIn the case of general categories, broad interpretation is allowed for fun and creative game play. For example, in the case of things commonly found in the kitchen that start with the letter K, both knife (a kitchen tool) or Kelp, (a type of food that is commonly cooked in kitchens around the world) are acceptable answers. \n \n</string>
    <string name="time_set_hint">Number Of Seconds</string>
    <string name="no_of_cats_hint">Number Of Categories</string>
    <string name="SettingsConfirmStr">MAKE CHANGES</string>
</resources>